(Howard:)I'm a grown man
with a Master's degree in Engineering!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Excuse me, Mr. Fancy-Pants.
(Howard's Mother(voice):)Want me to get you a popsicle?
(Howard:)Cherry, please.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I ate the cherry. All that's left is green.
You make me wanna kill myself.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
(Leonard:)Now they're just yelling about popsicles.
(Leonard:)- Sounds like Penny really got to him.
- I'm not surprised.
(Raj:)Despite his hard and crusty shell,
Howard is a very sensitive man.
(Raj:)Do you know he writes poetry?
(Raj:)Mostly about men from Nantucket
and hermits named Dave...
(Raj:)...but he does it with real sensitivity.
[LISPING]
Hey, Hofstadter.
Word around the plasma lab
is you built a robot?
- Yes, we did, Kripke.
- His name is Monte.
Well, if you have any delusions about
entering him against the Kripke Crippler...
...in the Southern California Robot Fighting
League Round Robin Invitational...
...AKA the SCRFLRRI...